[
  {
    "Front": "τάξις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: orden"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ταράττω",
    "Back": " vb.: forstyrrer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τάττω",
    "Back": " vb.: opstiller"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ταυτ-: : se οὗτος"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τάχος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: hurtighed"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ταχύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: hurtig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τε",
    "Back": " konj.: og (efterhængt)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τε - καί",
    "Back": " konj. $: både - og"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τείνω",
    "Back": " vb.: spænder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τεῖχος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: mur"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τεκµήριον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: tegn"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέκνον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: barn"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέλειος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: færdig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τελευτάω",
    "Back": " vb.: dør, slutter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τελευτή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: ende"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τελέω",
    "Back": " vb.: fuldbyrder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέλος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: (ende)mål"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέµνω",
    "Back": " vb.: skærer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέταρτος",
    "Back": " num. adj. 1-2: fjerde"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέτταρα",
    "Back": " num. indekl.: fire"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τετταράκοντα",
    "Back": " num. indekl.: fyrre"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τέχνη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: færdighed"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τηρέω",
    "Back": " vb.: bevogter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τίθηµι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: sætter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τίκτω",
    "Back": " vb.: føder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τιµάω",
    "Back": " vb.: ærer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τιµή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: værdi, ære"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τιν-: : se τίς eller τις"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τις",
    "Back": " pron.: nogen"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τίνω",
    "Back": " vb.: betaler"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τίς",
    "Back": " pron.: hvem"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τίσις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: betaling"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τοιοῦτος",
    "Back": " pron. 1-2 (ureg.): sådan"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τόµος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: snit"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τόνος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: spænding"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τόξον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: bue"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τόπος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: sted"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τοσοῦτος",
    "Back": " pron. 1-2 (ureg.): så stor"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τότε",
    "Back": " adv.: dengang"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τουτ-: : se οὗτος"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τραῦµα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: sår"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τραχύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: hård"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τρεῖς",
    "Back": " num. adj. 3: tre"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τρέπω",
    "Back": " vb.: vender"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τρέφω",
    "Back": " vb.: nærer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τρέχω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: løber"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τριάκοντα",
    "Back": " num. indekl.: tredive"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τρίτος",
    "Back": " num. adj. 1-2: tredje"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τρόπος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: vending"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τροφή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: føde"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τύγχάνω",
    "Back": " vb.: er tilfældigvis"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τύπος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: slag"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τύπτω",
    "Back": " vb.: slår"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τύραννος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: tyran"
  },
  {
    "Front": "τύχη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: tilfælde"
  }
]